BISMA SHAKIL

Karachi Pk | s.bismashakeel058@gmail.com | 03096839925

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

Passionate and dedicated teacher with a strong ability to foster a positive and engaging learning environment. Experienced in delivering clear, structured lessons and supporting diverse student needs. Committed to encouraging academic growth and building student confidence through patience, creativity, and effective communication.

EDUCATION:

MATRICULATION April 2018-March 2020

Brilliant Career School, Science Group

INTERMEDIATE September 2020-July 2022

BAMM PECHS Govt College for Women, Pre Med Group

PHARM-D January 2023-Present

University of Karachi, Karachi

WORK EXPERIENCE:

THE SMART SCHOOL

September 2022-April 2023

Taught Math's to Middle School students, strengthened communication and instructional skills by working closely with students of different learning levels.

HAPPY CHILD SCHOOL

September 2023-Present

Teaching Math's and Biology to Matric level students, creating custom lesson plans and practice tests to support student learning and academic improvement.

SKILLS:

- Effective Communication
- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)
- Internet & Email Handling
- Basic Design Tools